<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide App</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="Aberdeen"> Aberdeen is a city in northeast Scotland. It is Scotland third most populous city, one of Scotland 32 local government council areas and the United Kingdom 39th most populous built-up area, with an official 2018 population estimate of 198,880 for the city of Aberdeen and 227,560 for the local council area.During the mid-18th to mid-20th centuries, Aberdeen buildings incorporated locally quarried grey granite, which can sparkle like silver because of its high mica content.Since the discovery of North Sea oil in the 1970s, Aberdeen has been known as the off-shore oil capital of Europe. The area around Aberdeen has been settled for at least 8,000 years, when prehistoric villages lay around the mouths of the rivers Dee and Don. The city has a long, sandy coastline and a marine climate, the latter resulting in chilly summers and mild winters.Aberdeen received Royal burgh status from David I of Scotland , transforming the city economically. The city has two universities, the University of Aberdeen, founded in 1495, and Robert Gordon University, which was awarded university status in 1992, making Aberdeen the educational centre of north-east Scotland. The traditional industries of fishing, paper-making, shipbuilding, and textiles have been overtaken by the oil industry and Aberdeen seaport. Aberdeen Heliport is one of the busiest commercial heliports in the world and the seaport is the largest in the north-east of Scotland.</string>
    <string name="Sarasota"> Sarasota #1 in Best Places to Visit in Florida, is a city in Sarasota County on the southwestern coast of the U.S. state of Florida. The area is renowned for its cultural and environmental amenities, beaches, resorts, and the Sarasota School of Architecture. The city is at the southern end of the Tampa Bay Area, north of Fort Myers and Punta Gorda. Its official limits include Sarasota Bay and several barrier islands between the bay and the Gulf of Mexico. According to the U.S. Census Bureau, in 2019 Sarasota had a population of 58,285. In 1986 it became designated as a certified local government. Sarasota is a principal city of the Sarasota metropolitan area, and is the seat of Sarasota County. Long the winter headquarters of the Ringling Brothers Circus, many landmarks in Sarasota are named for the Ringlings. </string>
    <string name="Naples"> Naples #5 in Best Places to Visit in Florida , is the regional capital of Campania and the third-largest city of Italy, after Rome and Milan, with a population of 967,069 within the city administrative limits as of 2017. Its province-level municipality is the third-most populous metropolitan city in Italy with a population of 3,115,320 residents, and its metropolitan area (that stretches beyond the boundaries of the Metropolitan City of Naples) is the second-most populous metropolitan area in Italy and the 7th-most populous urban area in the European Union.First settled by Greeks in the first millennium BC, Naples is one of the oldest continuously inhabited urban areas in the world. In the ninth century BC, a colony known as Parthenope or Παρθενόπη was established on the Island of Megaride.In the 6th century BC, it was refounded as Neápolis. The city was an important part of Magna Graecia, played a major role in the merging of Greek and Roman society, and was a significant cultural centre under the Romans.</string>
    <string name="Miami"> Miami #6 in Best Places to Visit in Florida, Few places in the world compare to colorful, vibrant Miami Beach. From the art deco architecture along Ocean Drive to the scantily clad beachgoers on South Beach, this Miami offshoot attracts everyone from relaxed retirees to night owls. But you will want to bring along your credit card, because those fashionable dance clubs and chic, trendy restaurants don\'t come cheap. To save some money, consider buying a Go Miami card before your trip to access to some of the area museums and tours for a fraction of the price .Also officially the City of Miami, is a metropolis located in southeastern Florida in the United States. It is the second most populous metropolis on the East coast of the United States, and it is the seventh largest in the country.The city is an economic powerhouse, serving as the financial and business capital of Latin America. The city has the third tallest skyline in the U.S. with over 300 high-rises,55 of which exceed 491 ft (150 m).Miami is a major center and leader in finance, commerce, culture, arts, and international trade.The metro area is by far the largest urban economy in Florida and the 12th largest in the United States, with a GDP of $344.9 billion as of 2017. In 2020, Miami was classified as a Beta + level global city by the GaWC. In 2019, Miami ranked seventh in the United States and 31st among global cities in terms of business activity, human capital, information exchange, cultural experience, and political engagement.[16] According to a 2018 UBS study of 77 world cities, the city was ranked as the third-richest in the United States and the eighth-richest in the world in terms of purchasing power. Miami is nicknamed the \"Capital of Latin America\" and is the largest city with a Cuban-American plurality.</string>
    <string name="Augustine"> St.Augustine #8 in Best Places to Visit in Florida , is a city in the Southeastern United States, on the Atlantic coast of northeastern Florida. Founded in 1565 by Spanish explorers, it is the oldest continuously inhabited European-established settlement in the United States proper (San Juan, Puerto Rico was settled earlier, in 1521).St. Augustine was founded on September 8, 1565, by Spanish admiral Pedro Menéndez de Avilés, Florida first governor. He named the settlement , as his ships bearing settlers, troops, and supplies from Spain had first sighted land in Florida eleven days earlier on August 28, the feast day of St. Augustine. The city served as the capital of Spanish Florida for over 200 years. It was designated as the capital of British East Florida when the colony was established in 1763; Great Britain returned Florida to Spain in 1783.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="MountEverest"> Mount Everest Restaurant combines Nepalese and Indian Cuisine offering guests a delicious taste of Nepal, India and Tibet with Himalayan cooking at its core.The restaurant, located within the beautiful Aberdeenshire, is set in a comfortable, modern yet warm and friendly ambience for you to enjoy subtle and fresh taste of Himalayas. Guests can enjoy a variety of Nepalese and Indo-Tibetan menu designed and prepared freshly by our award winning chef, Bimal, using finest ingredients and spices.We cannot wait for you to try our fragrant curries, heart-warming dumplings called MOMOs and sizzling grilled dishes. We are great at take-outs and delivery, but are fantastic for DINING IN.
For reservation and take-outs/ delivery orders, please contact us via phone, email or online. We look forward to welcoming you to Mount Everest Restaurant in Blackburn, Aberdeen.</string>
    <string name="FloribbeanFlo">Floribbean Flo is a Florida Gift Basket Citrus and Bakery Company and Florida premier source of Florida gifts shipped and delivered for every occasion as well as a Tropical Bakery in Sarasota that features  Florida famous Key Lime Pie, other pies, cakes cookies and savories created with Florida foods and citrus fruits.</string>
    <string name="Mediterrano">Centrally located in the hustle and bustle of The Junction, this location offers a welcome, calmer change of pace while maintaining an exciting, vibrant atmosphere. Featuring exclusive deals unavailable at our other branches, this is an excellent venue for weekly plans and special occasions alike, a fun spot to see and be seen as you enjoy our impressive wine selection or signature cocktails.</string>
    <string name="ilPastaiolo">IL Pastaiolo is a trattoria Neapolitan style, hand tossed with our homemade Pasta. IL Pastaiolo holds on to the old traditions that will never change, we are constantly improving. Because of a great staff and an abundance of loyal customers we are proud to continue serving you.</string>
    <string name="Collage">When dining at Collage, be prepared for a first-class, award-winning experience. The menu reflects the eclectic tastes of owners Mike Hyatt and Cindy Stangby and focuses on fresh local seafood, steaks, lamb and veal, using international flavor profiles. Located just a block off of St. George Street in the heart of the historic district. Collage serves dinner nightly from 5:00 p.m.</string>
    <string name="hotel1">Sandman Signature Aberdeen Hotel is offering accommodation in Aberdeen. Among the various facilities are a shared lounge and a bar.At the hotel, all rooms are equipped with a desk and a flat-screen TV. The private bathroom is fitted with a shower. All units feature a private bathroom and free toiletries. Breakfast is available daily, and includes buffet options.Sandman Signature Aberdeen Hotel can conveniently provide information at the reception to help guests to get around the area. Popular points of interest near the accommodation include Beach Ballroom, Aberdeen Art Gallery and Bon Accord And St Nicholas. The nearest airport is Aberdeen Airport, 8 km from Sandman Signature Aberdeen Hotel.
    Couples particularly like the location — they rated it 9.3 for a two-person trip.We speak your language!</string>
    <string name="hotel2">Lovers of the Ritz-Carlton brand are very much impressed by the Sarasota, Florida, version. Even though they have come to expect top-notch service, plush rooms and classy ambiance from these properties, travelers still can not  stop gushing over the excellent customer service and the close attention to detail. At this Marriott affiliated property, accommodations impress with amenities like private balconies, goose-down pillows and 55-inch flat-screen TVs. The resort also boasts an 18-hole, Tom Fazio-designed golf course (15 miles off-site). For non-golfers, The Ritz-Carlton, Sarasota provides tennis courts; but if you would rather kick back and relax, you will also find a pool, a spa and a beach club</string>
    <string name="hotel3">This resort in northern Naples, Florida, is a big hit with families. Perhaps it is the pool with a 100-foot-long twisting waterslide or the 3 miles of white sand beach. But don not worry if you are traveling sans the youngsters; there are still plenty of amenities to pass the time. The property boasts an 18-hole golf course, 15 Har-Tru tennis courts and a spa with 12 treatment rooms. Grab a drink at the lounge, sit down to a tasty lunch at Aura Restaurant or head to The Catch of the Pelican for a delicious dinner of steak and seafood. When it is time to sleep, recharge in a coastal, garden or gulf view room. Each comes equipped with a private balcony or patio, a flat-screen TV and a marble bathroom with a walk-in shower and a soaking tub.</string>
    <string name="hotel4">The Faena Hotel Miami Beach is a historic resort hotel located at 3201 Collins Avenue Miami Beach.</string>
    <string name="hotel5">The Hilton Historic Bayfront hotel in historic downtown St. Augustine offers all the amenities of a modern Hilton hotel and all the charm of a historic location. This luxury hotel provides both meeting space and event space for special occasions. Whether you are traveling through on business, on a couple getaway or a fun family vacation there is the room for you at the Hilton Historic Bayfront hotel.
There is a large banquet space for 120 people, a fully equipped board room and a business center.</string>
    <string name="about">   is a state located in the southeastern region of the United States. With a population of over 21 million, Florida is the third-most populous and the 22nd-most extensive of the 50 United States. The state is bordered to the west by the Gulf of Mexico, to the northwest by Alabama, to the north by Georgia, to the east by the Atlantic Ocean, and to the south by the Straits of Florida. The state is capital is Tallahassee and its most populous municipality is Jacksonville. The Miami metropolitan area, with a population of almost 6.2 million, is the most populous urban area in Florida and the seventh-most populous in the United States. Other urban areas in the state with a population of more than one million are Tampa Bay, Orlando, and Jacksonville. Florida $1.0 trillion economy is the fourth-largest of any U.S. state, and if it were a country, Florida would be the 16th-largest economy in the world.
The first European contact was made in 1513 by Spanish explorer Juan Ponce de León, who called it la Florida ( "the land of flowers") upon landing there. At various points in its colonial history, Florida was administered by Spain and Great Britain. Florida was admitted as the 27th state on March 3, 1845. Florida was the principal location of the Seminole Wars (1816 – 1858), the longest and most extensive of Indian Wars in United States history. Florida declared its secession from the Union on January 10, 1861, and was one of the seven original Confederate States. After the Civil War, Florida was restored to the Union on June 25, 1868.Today, Florida is distinctive for its large Cuban expatriate community and high population growth, as well as for its increasing environmental issues. The state economy relies mainly on tourism, agriculture, and transportation, which developed in the late 19th century. Florida is also renowned for amusement parks, orange crops, winter vegetables, the Kennedy Space Center, and as a popular destination for retirees. It is the flattest state in the United States, and Lake Okeechobee is its largest freshwater lake.</string>
<string name="FLORIDA">GO FLORIDA</string>
    <string name="hotelinaberdeen">#1  Hotel in Aberdeen , $49 NIGHTLY RESORT FEE</string>
    <string name="sandmansignture">Sandman Signature Aberdeen Hotel \n</string>
    <string name="HotelinSarasota">#1  Hotel  in Sarasota , $37 NIGHTLY RESORT FEE</string>
    <string name="TheRitzCarlton">The Ritz-Carlton</string>
    <string name="HotelinNaples">#1  Hotel  in Naples , $175 NIGHTLY RESORT FEE</string>
    <string name="NaplesGrandeBeachResort">Naples Grande Beach Resort </string>
    <string name="HotelinMiami">#1  Hotel  in Miami Beach ,  $475 NIGHTLY RESORT FEE</string>
    <string name="Faena">Faena Hotel Miami Beach </string>
    <string name="hotelinAugustine">#1  Hotel  in St. Augustine ,  $194 NIGHTLY RESORT FEE</string>
    <string name="Hilton">Hilton St. Augustine Historic Bayfront  </string>
    <string name="StarkeBikefest">Starke Bikefest</string>
    <string name="Pensacola">Pensacola Interstate Fair</string>
    <string name="Twilight">Twilight Green Market at Wellington</string>
    <string name="TheGreatPumpkin">The Great Pumpkin</string>
    <string name="MiamiSpice">Miami Spice Restaurant Months</string>
    <string name="Aberdeenplace">Aberdeen</string>
    <string name="Sarasotaplace">Sarasota</string>
    <string name="Naplesplace">Naples </string>
    <string name="Miamiplace">Miami </string>
    <string name="Augustineplace">St.Augustine </string>
    <string name="MountEverestResturnat">Mount Everest</string>
    <string name="infoResturant1">#1 of 446 Restaurants in Aberdeen </string>
    <string name="infoResturant2">#1 of 894 Places to Eat in Sarasota</string>
    <string name="infoResturant3">#1 of 936 Places to Eat in Naples</string>
    <string name="infoResturant4">#1 of 967 Places to Eat in Miami Beach</string>
    <string name="infoResturant5">#1 of 565 Places to Eat in St. Augustine</string>
    <string name="Floribbean">Floribbean Flo\'s</string>
    <string name="MediterranoResturant">Mediterrano </string>
    <string name="Pastaiolo">il Pastaiolo </string>
    <string name="CollageResturnat">Collage Restaurant </string>
    <string name="Places">Places</string>
    <string name="Restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="Hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="Events">Events</string>
    <string name="About">About </string>
    <string name="latitiude">latitiude</string>
    <string name="Longitiude">Longitiude</string>
    <string name="yourdesiredlocation">Your Desired Location</string>
    <string name="tab1">Places</string>
    <string name="tab2">Resturants</string>
    <string name="tab3">Hotels</string>
    <string name="tab4">Events</string>
    <string name="tab5">About</string>
    <string name="resouce">resId</string>
    <string name="information">info</string>
    <string name="tabs">tab</string>

</resources>